Contact

maranrb@gmail.com +918754491334 LinkedIn Profile

Top Skills · See all

Information Security Management
· Networking · Virtualization
Solutions · ITIL · Security ·
Integration · Team Leadership ·
Team Building · Virtualization ·
Telecommunications

Accomplishments · See all

1 Language

Recommendations · See all

Ramesh P Independent Consultant at Headworth

Kanthasamy Pandian
VP - Telecom Delivery at Comnet
International

Maran R.B.

Associate Vice President - IT Security Sales at Raksha Technologies, Chennai

Tiruvallur, Tamil Nadu, India

Summary

An Electrical & Electronics Engineer with over 25 years of experience in IT Technical Sales, Project Management and also a qualified Solar PV Engineer, with expertise in the design, engineering, procurement, integration of KW scale off-grid and grid-tied PV power plants. Has profound knowledge & experience in sales & marketing, business & supply chain development, buildin...

Read more

Experience

Vice President Information Security · Raksha Technologies

August 2016 - Present · Chennai

Providing Sales leadership and enabling sales team to provide solutions in the areas of Endpoint Security, Network Security, Critical Hardware Security, DLP, Endpoint Management to Mobility, Mail & Web security, MDM, SIEM etc.

Promoter · SM Solar Infratech

June 2013 - Present

Promoting Solar Solutions with a mission to achieve 20 MW Solar Integration by 2020 and doing my little bit in the Renewable Energy mission of the Government. Certified for Solar PV Design & Installation. Industrial Solar solutions provided for:Rooftop Hybrid / Off-Grid / Grid-Tie Solar PV Systems.1 kWp to MW

VP - Sales · Nimis Group LLC

April 2015 - December 2015 (9 months)

Vice President - Business Development · Fourth Dimension

Technologies Pvt Ltd.

March 2011 - May 2013 (2 years 3 months) · Chennai

General Manager, Head -Networking & Information

Security · Precision Techserve Private Limited

2005 - March 2011 (6 years 3 months)

See all of Maran's experience



Contact

maranrb@gmail.com +918754491334 LinkedIn Profile

Top Skills · See all

Information Security Management
· Networking · Virtualization
Solutions · ITIL · Security ·
Integration · Team Leadership ·
Team Building · Virtualization ·
Telecommunications

Accomplishments · See all

1 Language

Recommendations · See all

Ramesh P Independent Consultant at Headworth

Kanthasamy Pandian
VP - Telecom Delivery at Comnet
International

Education

Jawahar Higher secondary school (1971 - 1985)

